**Warning**: include\_once(../\_include/svgs-flags.php): failed to open stream: No such file or directory in **/var/www/softorbits.com/\_include/templates.php** on line **209**  
  
**Warning**: include\_once(): Failed opening '../\_include/svgs-flags.php' for inclusion (include\_path='.:/usr/share/php') in **/var/www/softorbits.com/\_include/templates.php** on line **209**  
 SoftOrbits Privacy Policy English                                           

SoftOrbits

1. [Home](https://www.softorbits.net/) 
2. SoftOrbits Privacy Policy 

SoftOrbits Privacy Policy
=========================

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.

Log Files
---------

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Links to Other Websites
-----------------------

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

A Note About Website Cookies for the purpose of Remarketing
-----------------------------------------------------------

You should be aware that www.softorbits.com uses Google AdWords, Google Analytics, and the Google Display Network together to serve ads to you on other websites after you've visited our website. This practice is known as remarketing and is a tool that Google offers to businesses. But here are the basics: we, along with third-party vendors, Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

Security
--------

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100%% secure. Therefore—as is the case with any organization—we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

Legal Disclaimer
----------------

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website. By installing or using our products you agree to receive technical or marketing emails to provided email address.

Our products
------------

Microsoft, Windows are registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and other countries. Other names may be trademarks of their respective owners.

Join our Mailing List

Sign up for news and special offers

  Subscribe

Please confirm your email address.

Please fill all fields correctly.

Don't worry... we will never pass on your email address to third parties.

* * *

Copyright © 2024 SoftOrbits™ Co. Ltd. All rights reserved. [About Us](https://www.softorbits.net/about.html) | [Terms Of Use](https://www.softorbits.net/terms.html) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.softorbits.net/privacy-policy.html) | [Contacts](https://www.softorbits.net/support.html) | [Careers](https://www.softorbits.net/jobs.html)

Create Content Like a Pro, Effortlessly ★ Create Content Like a Pro, Effortlessly ★ Create Content Like a Pro, Effortlessly ★ Create Content Like a Pro, Effortlessly ★ Create Content Like a Pro, Effortlessly ★ Create Content Like a Pro, Effortlessly ★
